information-britain.co.uk 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy

## BACKGROUND:

Information-Britain.co.uk understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your information is used and shared online. We respect and value the privacy of everyone who visits Our Site and will only collect and use information in ways that are useful to you and in a manner consistent with your rights and our obligations under the law. 

This Privacy policy has been updated on May 24th 2018 in line with GDPR law commencing 25th May 2018. 

This Policy applies to our use of any and all data collected by us in relation to your use of Our Site. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and ensure that you understand it. Your acceptance of Our Privacy Policy is deemed to occur upon your first use of Our Site. If you do not accept and agree with this Privacy Policy, you must stop using Our Site immediately. 

## Definitions and Interpretation

In this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings: 

"Account"
    Means an account required to access and/or use certain areas and features of Our Site.
"Cookie"
    Means a small text file placed on your computer or device by Our Site when you visit certain parts of Our Site and/or when you use certain features of Our Site. Details of the Cookies used by Our Site can be obtained by request
"Cookie Law"
    Refers to the relevant parts of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003.
"Personal data"
    Means any and all data that relates to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified from that data. In this case, it means personal data that you give to Us via Our Site. This definition shall, where applicable, incorporate the definitions provided in the EU Regulation 2016/679 - the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR")
"Our Site"
    Means this website, information-britainco.uk.
"UK and EU Cookie Law"
    Means the relevant parts of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 as amended in 2004, 2011 and 2015.
"We/Us/Our"
    Information Britain PO Box 291, Beckenham, Kent, BR3 1XL

## Information About Us

Our Site, Information-Britain.co.uk, is owned and operated by Simon Waite T/A Heritage Britain, whose address is PO Box 291, Beckenham, Kent, BR3 1XL

Scope - What Does This Policy Cover?
    This Privacy Policy applies only to your use of Our Site. It does not extend to any websites that are linked to from Our Site (whether We provide those links or whether they are shared by other users). We have no control over how your data is collected, stored or used by other websites and We advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them.
What Data Do We Collect?
    The only data we collect is automatic through our use of cookies deployed to give you the best of experiences. This data is shared with 3rd party advertisers such as Google to ensure delivery of relevant ads. This is limited to IP address, Browser type and version and Operating System. We do not collect email addresses 
How Do We Use Your Data?
    The only data we collect is via Cookie which we then pass on to 3rd party advertisers automatically. We do not store your data but 3rd party advertisers might. We accept no responsibility for how a company such as Google may use your data and if you have concerns we suggest that you read their privacy policy. 

## What Cookies Do we Use and What For?

By using Our Site you will also receive certain third party Cookies on your computer or device. Third party Cookies are those placed by websites, services, and/or parties other than Us. We use third party Cookies on Our Site for advertising services. These Cookies are not integral to the functioning of Our Site. 

  * All Cookies used by and on Our Site are used in accordance with current UK and EU Cookie Law.
  * Before certain Cookies are placed on your computer or device, you will be shown a prompt requesting your consent to set those Cookies. By giving your consent to the placing of Cookies you are enabling Us to provide the best possible experience and service to you. You may, if you wish, deny consent to the placing of Cookies; however certain features of Our Site may not function fully or as intended.
  * [Certain features of Our Site depend on Cookies to function. UK and EU Cookie Law deems these Cookies to be "strictly necessary". Your consent will not be sought to place these Cookies. You may still block these cookies by changing your internet browser's settings, but please be aware that Our Site may not work as intended if you do so. We have taken great care to ensure that your privacy is not at risk by allowing them.] 
  * There are various first party Cookies may be placed on your computer or device, please contact us for a comprehensive list of these.
  * You can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser. Most internet browsers also enable you to choose whether you wish to disable all cookies or only third party Cookies. By default, most internet browsers accept Cookies but this can be changed. For further details, please consult the help menu in your internet browser or the documentation that came with your device.
  * You can choose to delete Cookies at any time however you may lose any information that enables you to access Our Site more quickly and efficiently including, but not limited to, login and personalisation settings.
  * It is recommended that you keep your internet browser and operating system up-to-date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser and manufacturer of your computer or device if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about Our Site or this Privacy Policy or the cookies we use, please contact Us by email at [mail@heritagebritain.com](mailto:mail@heritagebritain.com), or by telephone on +44(0)208 658 9111, or by post at Heritage Britain, PO Box 291, Beckenham, Kent, BR3 1XL. Please ensure that your query is clear, particularly if it is a request for information about the data We hold about you

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy as we may deem necessary from time to time, or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on Our Site and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the Privacy Policy on your first use of Our Site following the alterations. We recommend that you check this page regularly to keep up-to-date.

Thanks for reading!

**Brit Quote:**  
The snowdrop and primrose our woodlands adorn, and violets bathe in the wet o' the morn. - Robert Burns  
More Quotes  
  
---  
  
**On this day:**  
Battle of Adwalton Moor - 1643, The Great Stink at its Worst - 1858, Night of the Long Knives - 1934, German Troops invade Channel Islands - 1940, First Harry Potter Book Published - 1997, Terror Attack on Glasgow Airport - 2007  
More dates from British history
